<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Rights</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="vote_details">\t1. The right to vote is a fundamental human right that enables citizens to participate in the democratic process by selecting their representatives and shaping government policies.\n\n \t2.In many countries, the right to vote has been restricted or denied to certain groups based on factors such as gender, race, ethnicity.\n\n \t3.Universal suffrage, which guarantees the right to vote to all adult citizens regardless of their background or identity, is an essential aspect of a functioning democracy.\n\n \t4.Ensuring that everyone has equal access to the right to vote requires efforts to eliminate barriers such as voter suppression, discriminatory voter ID laws, and unequal access to polling stations.\n\n</string>
    <string name="text_violation">\t• Refers to actions or policies that infringe on an individual\'s basic human rights or civil liberties.\n\n \t• Examples of rights that may be violated include freedom of speech, freedom of religion, and the right to be free from discrimination.\n\n \t• Violations of rights can be committed by individuals, organizations, or governments.\n\n \t• In some cases, violations of rights can be addressed through legal remedies such as filing a lawsuit or seeking a court order.\n\n \t• Protecting individual rights is a fundamental principle of many legal systems, and violations of rights are often seen as a serious breach of ethical and legal standards.\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_equality">Equality</string>

    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->
    <string name="first_fragment_label">First Fragment</string>
    <string name="second_fragment_label">Second Fragment</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="previous">Previous</string>


    <string name="text_equality">\t1. The right to equality ensures that all individuals are treated equally under the law, without discrimination or prejudice.\n\n\t2. Discrimination on any ground, such as race, gender, religion, and sexual orientation, is strictly prohibited under the right to equality.\n\n\t3. The right to equality is essential to promote social justice, eliminate poverty, and advance sustainable development.\n\n\t4. The right to equality includes access to education, healthcare, employment, and other essential services without discrimination.\n\n\t5. The right to equality is protected by international and national laws and institutions, including courts and human rights bodies.\n</string>
    <string name="Article15">\t• Everyone has the right to a nationality.\n\n \t• No one shall be arbitrarily deprived of their nationality nor denied the right to change their nationality.\n\n \t• Men and women have the equal right to pass their nationality to their children.\n\n \t• Every person has the right to enter and leave any country, including their own, and this right shall not be restricted except in accordance with law.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to own property alone as well as in association with others, and no one shall be arbitrarily deprived of their property.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article14">\t• Everyone has the right to seek and enjoy asylum from persecution in other countries.\n\n \t• This right cannot be invoked in the case of prosecutions genuinely arising from non-political crimes or from acts contrary to the purposes and principles of the United Nations.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to a fair and public hearing by an independent and impartial tribunal, in the determination of their rights and obligations and of any criminal charge against them.\n\n \t• Everyone charged with a criminal offence shall be presumed innocent until proven guilty according to law in a public trial where they have had all the guarantees necessary for their defense.\n\n \t• No one shall be subjected to arbitrary arrest, detention, or exile.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article16">\t• Men and women of full age, without any limitation due to race, nationality, or religion, have the right to marry and to found a family.\n\n \t• They are entitled to equal rights as to marriage, during marriage, and at its dissolution.\n\n \t• Marriage shall be entered into only with the free and full consent of the intending spouses.\n\n \t• The family is the natural and fundamental group unit of society and is entitled to protection by society and the State.\n\n \t• No one shall be subjected to arbitrary interference with their family, home, or correspondence, nor to attacks upon their honor and reputation.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article17">\t• Everyone has the right to own property alone as well as in association with others\n\n. \t• No one shall be arbitrarily deprived of their property.\n\n \t• Property rights shall be protected by law.\n\n \t• No one shall be deprived of their property except when it is necessary for public use and provided that they receive just and fair compensation.\n\n \t• The right to own property may be subject to limitations necessary for the general welfare or in order to secure the payment of taxes or other contributions or penalties.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article18">\t• Everyone has the right to freedom of thought, conscience, and religion.\n\n \t• This right includes freedom to change their religion or belief, and freedom, either alone or in community with others and in public or private, to manifest their religion or belief in teaching, practice, worship, and observance.\n\n \t• No one shall be forced to adopt a particular religion or belief.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to freedom of thought and conscience, and this right includes the freedom to hold opinions without interference and to seek, receive, and impart information and ideas through any media and regardless of frontiers.\n\n \t• The exercise of these rights may be subject to restrictions that are necessary to protect public safety, order, health, or morals or the fundamental rights and freedoms of others.\n\n</string>
    <string name="text_freedom">\t1. The right to freedom is a fundamental human right that includes freedom of speech, religion, assembly, and association.\n\n \t2. The right to freedom also includes the right to privacy, the right to a fair trial, and the right to seek asylum.\n\n \t3. The right to freedom is essential for the protection of human dignity, individual autonomy, and the promotion of democracy.\n\n \t4. The right to freedom is protected by international and national laws and institutions, including courts and human rights bodies.\n\n \t5. The right to freedom may be subject to certain limitations, such as for the protection of public order, national security, and the rights of others.\n</string>
    <string name="Article19">\t• Everyone has the right to freedom of opinion and expression.\n\n \t• This right includes freedom to hold opinions without interference and to seek, receive, and impart information and ideas through any media and regardless of frontiers.\n\n \t• The exercise of this right may be subject to certain restrictions, but only those provided by law and necessary for respect of the rights or reputations of others, or for the protection of national security or of public order or of public health or morals.\n\n \t• Freedom of expression includes the freedom to express one\'s opinions without interference, to seek and receive information and ideas.\n\n \t• The right to freedom of expression is a fundamental human right that is essential for the functioning of a democratic society and for the promotion and protection of other human rights.\n</string>
    <string name="Article20">• Everyone has the right to freedom of peaceful assembly and association.\n\n \t• No one may be compelled to belong to an association.\n\n \t• The exercise of these rights may be subject to certain restrictions, but these shall only be such as are provided by law and are necessary in a democratic society in the interests of national security or public safety, public order, the protection of public health or morals or the protection of the rights and freedoms of others.\n\n \t• The right to freedom of association includes the right to form and join trade unions for the protection of one\'s interests.\n\n \t• The right to freedom of peaceful assembly includes the right to gather for peaceful demonstrations, protests, and meetings, and to express one\'s opinions in a public forum without fear of persecution or retaliation.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article21">\t• Everyone has the right to take part in the government of their country, directly or through freely chosen representatives.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to equal access to public service in their country.\n\n \t• The will of the people shall be the basis of the authority of government.\n\n \t• This will shall be expressed in periodic and genuine elections, which shall be by universal and equal suffrage and shall be held by secret ballot or by equivalent free voting procedures.\n\n \t• The right to vote and to be elected in genuine periodic elections is a fundamental human right that is essential for the functioning of a democratic society and for the promotion and protection of other human rights.\n</string>
    <string name="Article22">\t• Everyone has the right to freedom of association with others, including the right to form and join trade unions for the protection of their interests.\n\n \t• No one may be compelled to belong to an association.\n\n \t• The exercise of this right may be subject to certain restrictions, but only those provided by law and necessary in a democratic society in the interests of national security or public safety, public order, the protection of public health or morals or the protection of the rights and freedoms of others.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to form and join organizations that promote and protect human rights.\n\n \t• The right to freedom of association is a fundamental human right that is essential for the functioning of a democratic society and for the promotion and protection of other human rights.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article24">\t• Everyone has the right to the highest attainable standard of physical and mental health.\n\n \t• States have a responsibility to ensure access to medical care and necessary social services, regardless of economic or social status.\n\n \t• States must take measures to prevent, treat, and control epidemic, endemic, occupational, and other diseases.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to information and education on health-related issues.\n\n \t• States must ensure the provision of safe and healthy working conditions, and protect workers in hazardous occupations.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article23">\t• Everyone has the right to work, to free choice of employment, to just and favorable conditions of work and to protection against unemployment.\n\n \t• Everyone, without any discrimination, has the right to equal pay for equal work.\n\n \t• Everyone who works has the right to just and favorable remuneration, ensuring for themselves and their family an existence worthy of human dignity, and supplemented, if necessary, by other means of social protection.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to form and join trade unions for the protection of their interests.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to rest and leisure, including reasonable limitation of working hours and periodic holidays with pay.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Text_Exploitation">\t1. The right against exploitation is a fundamental human right that prohibits all forms of forced labor, child labor, and human trafficking.\n\n \t2. The right against exploitation also includes the prohibition of employment of children in hazardous occupations or industries.\n\n \t3. The right against exploitation is essential for protecting vulnerable groups from exploitation and abuse.\n\n \t4. The right against exploitation is protected by international and national laws and institutions, including courts and human rights bodies.\n\n \t5. The right against exploitation requires governments and other institutions to adopt measures to prevent and eliminate all forms of exploitation. \n</string>
    <string name="Article25">\t• Everyone has the right to a standard of living adequate for the health and well-being of themselves and their family, including food, clothing, housing, medical care, and necessary social services.\n\n \t• Mothers and children are entitled to special care and assistance, before and after birth.\n\n \t• All children, regardless of their parents\' status, have the right to equal social protection.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to security in the event of unemployment, sickness, disability, widowhood, old age, or other lack of livelihood in circumstances beyond their control.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to education, which shall be free, at least in the elementary and fundamental stages. Elementary education shall be compulsory.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article26">\t• Everyone has the right to education, which shall be directed to the full development of the human personality and to the strengthening of respect for human rights and fundamental freedoms.\n\n \t• Education shall be free, at least in the elementary and fundamental stages.\n\n \t• Education shall be compulsory and available to all.\n\n \t• Higher education shall be equally accessible to all on the basis of merit.\n\n \t• Education shall promote understanding, tolerance, and friendship among all nations, racial or religious groups, and shall further the activities of the United Nations for the maintenance of peace.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article27">\t• Everyone has the right to freely participate in the cultural life of the community, to enjoy the arts and to share in scientific advancement and its benefits.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to the protection of the moral and material interests .\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to the freedom of thought, conscience, including the freedom to change their religion or belief, and the freedom, either alone or in community with others and in public or private, to manifest their religion or belief in teaching, practice and worship\n\n \t• No one may be compelled to belong to an association or to attend a religious ceremony or rite.\n\n \t• The right to enjoy and participate in cultural life is a fundamental human right that is essential for the full development of the human personality and for the promotion and protection of other human rights.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article28">\t• Everyone is entitled to a social and international order in which the rights and freedoms set forth in the Declaration can be fully realized.\n\n \t• Everyone has a duty to promote respect for the rights and freedoms set forth in the Declaration.\n\n \t• No provision in the Declaration can be interpreted as implying for any State, group or person any right to engage in any activity or to perform any act aimed at the destruction of any of the rights and freedoms set forth in the Declaration.\n\n \t• Nothing in the Declaration shall be construed as implying for any State, group or person any right to engage in any activity or to perform any act aimed at the limitation of any of the rights and freedoms set forth in the Declaration.\n\n \t• The provisions of the Declaration are universal and apply equally to all human beings, regardless of race, color, sex or other opinion, national or social origin, property, birth or other status.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article29">\t• In the exercise of their rights and freedoms, everyone shall be subject only to such limitations as are determined by law solely for the purpose of securing due recognition and respect for the rights and freedoms of others and of meeting the just requirements of morality, public order, and the general welfare in a democratic society.\n\n \t• These rights and freedoms may in no case be exercised contrary to the purposes and principles of the United Nations.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to education, which shall be directed to the full development of the human personality and to the strengthening of respect for human rights and fundamental freedoms.\n\n \t• Everyone has a responsibility to respect the rights and freedoms of others and to promote the principles of tolerance, understanding, and peaceful coexistence.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article30">\t• The Declaration does not grant any State, group, or individual the right to engage in activities that aim to destroy any of the rights and freedoms mentioned in the Declaration.\n\n \t• No State, group, or individual can undertake any activities or perform any acts that aim to limit or curtail the rights and freedoms mentioned in the Declaration.\n\n \t• The rights and freedoms mentioned in the Declaration are universal, meaning that they apply to everyone.\n\n \t• The rights and freedoms mentioned in the Declaration are inalienable, which means that they cannot be taken away or surrendered by any person or authority.\n\n \t• The rights and freedoms mentioned in the Declaration are indivisible, meaning that they are interdependent and interrelated and that the violation of one right can have a cascading effect on the enjoyment of other rights.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article32">\t• Everyone has the right to leave any country, including their own, and to return to their country.\n\n \t• No one shall be arbitrarily deprived of the right to enter their own country.\n\n \t• These rights can only be subject to restrictions that are provided by law and are necessary to protect national security, public order, public health or morals, or the rights and freedoms of others.\n\n \t• No one shall be subjected to arbitrary interference with their privacy, family, home, or correspondence, nor to attacks on their honor or reputation.\n\n \t• Everyone has the right to protection against such interference or attacks.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Text_Religion">\t1. The right to freedom of religion is a fundamental human right that includes the freedom to practice, worship, and observe one\'s religion or belief without interference or coercion.\n\n 2. The right to freedom of religion also includes the freedom to change one\'s religion.\n\n \t3. The right to freedom of religion is essential for the protection of human dignity.\n\n \t4. The right to freedom of religion is protected by international and national laws and institutions, including courts and human rights bodies.\n\n \t5. The right to freedom of religion may be subject to certain limitations, such as for the protection of public safety, order, health, or morals .</string>
    <string name="Text_Cultural">\t1. Cultural and educational rights are fundamental human rights that protect an individual\'s right to participate in and benefit from cultural and educational activities.\n\n \t2. Cultural rights protect an individual\'s right to participate in cultural life and enjoy the benefits of their own culture, including language, religion, and traditions.\n\n \t3. Educational rights protect an individual\'s right to education and ensure that education is accessible, available, and of good quality.\n\n \t4. Cultural and educational rights are essential for the promotion of diversity, intercultural dialogue, and social cohesion.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Text_Remedies">\t1. The right to constitutional remedies is a fundamental human right that enables individuals to seek legal redress for the violation of their rights.\n\n \t2. The right to constitutional remedies provides individuals with access to effective and timely remedies, including through courts and other legal mechanisms.\n\n \t3. The right to constitutional remedies is essential for ensuring the rule of law, accountability, and the protection of human rights.\n\n \t4. The right to constitutional remedies is protected by international and national laws and institutions, including courts and human rights bodies.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Article326">\t• A legal order that requires a person who is detained or imprisoned to be brought before a court or judge.\n\n \t• Used to ensure that the detention or imprisonment is lawful and that the person\'s rights are being respected.\n\n \t• Typically used when a person believes that they are being held in violation of their constitutional rights, such as their right to due process or their right to a fair trial.\n\n \t• Requires a demonstration that the detention or imprisonment is unlawful or that the person\'s rights are being violated.\n\n \t• Available as a legal writ in common law jurisdictions such as the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Text_Habeas">\t• A legal order that requires a person who is detained or imprisoned to be brought before a court or judge.\n\n \t• Used to ensure that the detention or imprisonment is lawful and that the person\'s rights are being respected.\n\n \t• Typically used when a person believes that they are being held in violation of their constitutional rights, such as their right to due process or their right to a fair trial.\n\n \t• Requires a demonstration that the detention or imprisonment is unlawful or that the person\'s rights are being violated.\n\n \t• Available as a legal writ in common law jurisdictions such as the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom.\n\n</string>
    <string name="Text_Mandamus">\t• A legal order issued by a court that requires a public official or government agency to perform a specific duty that is required by law.\n\n \t• Used to compel government officials to perform their duties or to enforce a legal right or remedy.\n\n \t• Typically used when there is no other adequate legal remedy available to address the issue.\n\n \t• Requires a demonstration that the government official or agency has a legal duty to perform the specific action and that they have failed to do so.\n\n \t• Available as a legal writ in common law jurisdictions such as the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom.\n</string>
    <string name="Certoria">\t• A legal order issued by a higher court that grants review of a lower court decision.\n\n \t• Used to determine whether the lower court decision was made in accordance with the law and legal procedures.\n\n \t• Typically used in cases where the lower court decision involves an important legal issue or question of constitutional interpretation.\n\n \t• Requires a demonstration that there are significant legal issues or errors in the lower court decision that warrant further review.\n\n \t• Available as a legal writ in common law jurisdictions such as the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom.\n</string>
    <string name="TextQuoWarranto">\t• Requires a person or organization to show by what legal authority they are exercising a particular right or privilege.\n\n \t• Used to challenge the legal authority of public officials, corporations, or other organizations.\n\n \t• Aimed at preventing individuals or organizations from exercising powers or privileges that they do not have the legal authority to possess.\n\n \t• Requires a demonstration that the individual or organization being challenged is exercising powers or privileges that they do not have the legal authority to possess.\n\n \t• Available as a legal writ in some common law jurisdictions, such as the United States, Canada, and the United Kingdom.\n</string>
    <string name="Text_Prohibition">\t• A legal order issued by a higher court that prohibits a lower court or other judicial or quasi-judicial body from continuing to exercise jurisdiction over a particular matter.\n\n \t• Used to prevent a lower court or other body from exceeding its jurisdiction or acting in excess of its legal authority.\n\n \t• Typically used when a lower court or other body is threatening to take action that would result in irreparable harm.\n\n \t• Requires a demonstration that there is no other adequate legal remedy available to address the issue and that the lower court or body has acted in excess of its jurisdiction or legal authority.\n\n</string>

    <string name="lorem">Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, consectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua. Ut enim ad minim veniam</string>
    <string name="heading_one">About Us</string>
    <string name="heading_two">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="heading_three">Our Vision</string>
</resources>